#### Patchy is a free PowerShell module made by [Start-Automating](http://start-automating.com) that helps smooth out the chop of maintaining Windows Updates.  


It lets you find required and recommended patches by name, date, and update type.   You can use Patchy to determine what patches have already been applied to a machine, and can tell if your machine requires a reboot.   Patchy makes scripting patch management almost painless.  (almost).
